========================================================

Fake name, email and phone generator is perfect for filling a form, finding your baby name or writing a fiction story. Give it a try!

Privacy
=======

We have spent 3 years collecting data from every country to generate this enormous database. These numbers speak for themselves:

* 34 610 **Male** names
* 43 115 **Female** names
* 420 405 **Phone** numbers
* 23 900 **Companies**
* 82 different **Countries**
* over a **Billion** random names and profiles!

It is a perfect tool for generating a fake address, random phone number, fake email, random username and password. We can even generate fake payment details for Visa, MasterCard, American Express and even IBAN.

Collin Miller, age 32 says, _“This tool is so good at faking data that no validator can tell it is fake!”_

Privacy policy
--------------

### **Last updated: 16/12/2018**GENERAL

RandomNameGenerator operates https://www.random-name-generator.com/ website which provide a Phone Call or SMS know your caller number services and used by numerous Users. The following Privacy Policy apply when you view or use the RandomNameGenerator service through our website  
  
This privacy policy page informs you of RandomNameGenerator policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from buyers or users on RandomNameGenerator website.  
The terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, which is accessible at https://www.random-name-generator.com/ unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy.  
However, we use your Personal Information only for providing and improving RandomNameGenerator website.  
By using RandomNameGenerator website, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this privacy policy.  

### INFORMATION WE COLLECT & USE

While using RandomNameGenerator website, we may ask you to provide certain personally identifiable information that will be used to contact or identify you regarding our future offers and promotions. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to your name and Personal data  
We require all these information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, especially for the following reasons:  
1\. We use your information for internal record keeping.  
2\. We may use your information to improve our services and website.  
3\. We may periodically send promotional emails about new features, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.  
4\. From time to time, we may use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, or mail.  
5\. We may use your information to customize RandomNameGenerator website according to your interests.  

### LOG DATA

Like many website operators, RandomNameGenerator collects information that your browser sends whenever you visit RandomNameGenerator website  
This Log Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol ("IP") address, Browser type, browser version, the pages of RandomNameGenerator website that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.  
In addition, we may use third party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor and analyze all these above  

### CONTACT & COMMUNICATIONS

By using RandomNameGenerator website you do so at your own discretion and provide any such personal details requested at your own risk. Please note that your personal information is kept private and stored securely until a time it is no longer required or has no use, as detailed in the Data Protection Act 1998.  
Every effort has been made to ensure a safe and secure form to email submission process but we advise users using such form to email processes that they do so at their own risk.  
RandomNameGenerator solely use the information obtain to provide you with further information and good browsing experience to assist you in answering any questions or queries you may have submitted.  
This includes using your details to subscribe you to our email newsletter program marketing or promotional materials and other information that we deem necessary for you;  
But only if this was made clear to you and your express permission was granted when submitting any form to email process. Or whereby you the user have previously purchased from or enquired about purchasing from the RandomNameGenerator product that the email newsletter relates to.  
This is by no means an entire list of your user rights in regard to receiving email marketing material. However your details are not passed on to any third parties.  

### COOKIES

RandomNameGenerator website uses cookies to enhance users experience and functionality while using RandomNameGenerator website. However we employ the use of cookies where applicable,  
However some of our affiliate /advertising partners may also use cookies. This complies with recent legislation requirements for all websites to obtain explicit consent from users before leaving behind or reading files such as cookies on a user's computer / device.  
Users are advised that if they wish to deny the use and saving of cookies from RandomNameGenerator website on to their computers hard drive they should take necessary steps within their web browsers security settings to block all cookies from RandomNameGenerator website and its external serving vendors.  

### SERVICE PROVIDERS

RandomNameGenerator may employ third-party companies and individuals due to the following reasons:  

* To facilitate our products;
* To provide the RandomNameGenerator products on our behalf;
* To perform Service-related RandomNameGenerator or
* To assist us in analyzing how RandomNameGenerator website is used.

### We want to inform our users that these third parties have access to your Personal Information. The reason is to perform the tasks assigned to them on our behalf. However, they are obligated not to disclose or use the information for any other purpose.  
However, if you do not accept cookies from RandomNameGenerator website, you may not be able to use some portions of RandomNameGenerator website.SECURITY

RandomNameGenerator is committed to ensuring that your information is secure. The security of your Personal Information is important to us; In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure’ RandomNameGenerator has put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect in RandomNameGenerator website.  
But remember that no method of Transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, Dig Caller cannot guarantee its absolute security.  

### LINKS TO OTHER SITES

RandomNameGenerator products may contain links to other sites. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that site. Note that these external sites are not operated by us.  
Therefore, we strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of these websites. We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites or products.  

### CHILDREN’S PRIVACY

RandomNameGenerator website do not address anyone under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personal identifiable information from children under 13. In the case we discover that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we immediately delete this from our servers.  
If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with personal information, please contact us so that we will be able to do necessary actions.  

### VARIATION

RandomNameGenerator Privacy Policy is effective as of 25/01/2017 and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page.  
RandomNameGenerator reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of our website or services after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.  
If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, RandomNameGenerator will notify you either through the email address you provided us, or by placing a prominent notice on RandomNameGenerator website.

### CONTACT US

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at. https://www.random-name-generator.com/  

© 2024 Random-Name-Generator.com

x
